

MAHMOUD KASSEM

Lead Software Developer

Contacts

+20-1000-2153-50

mahmoud.ali.kassem@gmail.com

Alexandria, Egypt.

LinkedIn: mahmoud-kassem

LinkedIn: mahkassem

Education

LICENSE / LAW
Alexandria Univeristy
2006 – 2010

Skills

PHP - Laravel & C# - dotnet

JS – Angular – React – Vue NodeJS – NestJS

Design – Photoshop

Prototyping – Adobe XD - Figma

Management – Git – Trello – Jira Zoom – MS Teams – Skype Slack

Profile

Highly skilled web developer. I got a set of experiences covering both front-end/back-end and DevOps frameworks and technologies. I like to be creative. I'm learning new technologies to fulfill my passion and to keep up-to-date with the market requirements.

Work Experience

Team Leader

Alexandria For Programming / 2018 - Present

- Conduct daily and occasionally meetings with development team, designers, and project manager.
- Supervise development team, using GitLab, Jira and Slack.
- Testing and inspecting quality of code.
- Creating a documented Postman collection for API.
- Setup Hosting Servers and Deploy Apps.

FullStack Developer

GlobiSoft / 2016 - 2018

- Development of web sites/apps.
- Design Databases.
- Developing APIs for mobile and web apps.
- Setup and maintain Hosting Servers.
- Performing Tests for new recruits.